Archibald M. Crossley Papers 1999.0007
Archives & Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Libraries
- Series I: Consumer Studies, undated, 1927-1969
  - Subseries C: Various, undated, 1928-1969
    - Abbott Kimball Co., Inc.
      - Silk Consumer Study (dyers and finishers), 1947 [December] (Box 12:, Folder 451)
      - Silk Consumer Study (Manufacturers), 1947 [December] (Box 12:, Folder 452)
      - Silk Consumer Study (Retailers), 1947 [December] (Box 12:, Folder 453)
    - Ahrens Publishing Co.--Hotel Construction, Enlargement, and Modernization Study: Albany, NY, 1945 June (Box 12:, Folder 454)
    - [Allis-Chalmers]--Amphibious Vehicle Study, 1963 April (Box 12:, Folder 455)
    - Al Paul Lefton, Inc.--Whiskey Taste Preference Study, 1950 February (Box 12:, Folder 456)
    - American Airlines--Air Travel Market Study Proposal, undated (Box 12:, Folder 457)
    - [ American Gas Association]--Consumer Attitude Toward Gas and Gas Appliances Study, undated (Box 12:, Folder 458)
    - American Textile Co., Inc.
      - Study of Lace, 1950 July (Box 12:, Folder 459)
      - Study of Lace, 1950 October (Box 12:, Folder 460)
      - Lace Study (Richmond), 1951 February (Box 12:, Folder 461)
      - Lace Study (Savannah), 1951 February (Box 12:, Folder 462)
      - Lace Study (Southern Cities), 1951 February (Box 12:, Folder 463)
    - American Transit Association--Consumer Choice for Local Transportation Study Proposal, undated (Box 12:, Folder 464)
    - Anderson, Davis, and Hyde, Inc.--Alexander Smith-Shoreham Axminster Rugs Survey, 1931 October (Box 12:, Folder 465)
    - Anderson, Davis and Platte, Inc.--Post-War Floor Covering Study, 1944 [May] (Box 12:, Folder 466)
    - Anderson, Davis and Platte, Inc.--Traffic Character with Relation to Banking Habits Study, 1945 Feb (Box 12:, Folder 467)
    - Antony Gibbs and Co., Inc.--American Consumer Habits Pilot Study, 1938 August (Box 12:, Folder 468)
    - Armour and Co.--National Public Attitudes Survey Proposal, 1946 July (Box 12:, Folder 469)
    - Armstrong Cork Co.--Research Proposal, 1953 February (Box 12:, Folder 470)
    - Atlanta Gas Light Co.--Post-War Gas Survey (no tabulations), undated (Box 12:, Folder 471)
    - Automotive News--Research Proposal, 1954 July (Box 12:, Folder 472)
    - Bethlehem Steel Co.--Bethlehem Advertisement Effectiveness Study, [1938] (Box 12:, Folder 473)
    - Borden Co.--Consumer Awareness of Store Front Signs in Ice Cream Advertising Pre-Test, 1947 June (Box 12:, Folder 474)
    - Brand Index Corp.--Sales Analysis of Cigarette Brands Study (tabulations only), 1938 July (Box 12:, Folder 475)
    - Bridgeport Brass Co.--Cookware Market Pilot Study, 1949 November (Box 12:, Folder 476)
    - British Export Trade Research Organization--Edible Gelatin Study (tabulations only), 1948 April - May (Box 12:, Folder 477)
    - Burlington Mills--Advertising Attitude Study (tabulations only), 1950 June (Box 12:, Folder 478)
    - Business Council for International Understanding-- United States Bureau of International Commerce Publications Study Proposal (correspondences only), 1969 November - December (Box 12:, Folder 479)
    - Campbell Soup Co.--Survey Proposal, 1948 August (Box 12:, Folder 480)
    - Cecil and Presby, Inc.--Lighter Accessories Distribution and Sales Survey, 1948 September (Box 12:, Folder 481)
    - Celanese Corporation of America--Trends in Fabric Sales Study, 1953 October (Box 12:, Folder 482)
    - Charles Dallas Reach--Chicago Telephone Study, 1953 November (Box 12:, Folder 483)
    - Chase National Bank
      - Bank Attitude Study, Graybar Branch, 1953 November 11 (Box 12:, Folder 484)
      - Bank Attitude Study, Graybar Branch, 1953 November 18 (Box 12:, Folder 485)
      - Bank Attitude Study, 23rd St./Fifth Ave. Branch, 1953 December (Box 12:, Folder 486)
      - Bank Attitude Study, 34th St. Branch, 1953 December (Box 12:, Folder 487)
      - Bank Attitude Study, 34th St. Branch (office interviews), 1953 December (Box 12:, Folder 488)
      - Bank Attitude Study, East 42nd St. Branch, 1953 December (Box 12:, Folder 489)
      - Bank Attitude Study, East 42nd St. Branch (office interviews), 1953 December (Box 12:, Folder 490)
      - Bank Attitude Study, 48th St. Branch, 1953 December (Box 12:, Folder 491)
      - Bank Attitude Study, 48th St. Branch (office interviews), 1953 December (Box 12:, Folder 492)
      - Bank Attitude Study, 73rd St./Broadway Branch, 1953 December (Box 12:, Folder 493)
      - Bank Attitude Study, Broadway Branch, 1953 December (Box 12:, Folder 494)
      - Bank Attitude Study, Broadway Branch (office interviews), 1953 December (Box 12:, Folder 495)
      - Bank Attitude Study, Maiden Lane Branch, 1953 December (Box 12:, Folder 496)
      - Bank Attitude Study, Time Square Branch, 1953 December 11 (Box 12:, Folder 497)
      - Bank Attitude Study, Time Square Branch, 1953 December 28 (Box 12:, Folder 498)
      - Bank Attitude Study, Worth St./Broadway Branch (tabulations only), 1953 December (Box 12:, Folder 499)
      - Bank Attitude Study, 45th St. Branch, 1954 January (Box 12:, Folder 500)
      - Bank Attitude Study, 45th St. Branch (office interviews), 1954 January (Box 12:, Folder 501)
      - Bank Attitude Study, Rockefeller Center Branch, 1954 January (Box 12:, Folder 502)
      - Bank Attitude Study, Rockefeller Center Branch (office interviews), 1954 January (Box 12:, Folder 503)
      - Bank Attitude Study, 1954 January (Box 12:, Folder 504)
    - Cheney Brothers--Trade Survey on Men's Robes, 1948 April - May (Box 13:, Folder 505)
    - Congoleum-Nairn, Inc.
      - Floor Covering Design Survey (no tabulations), 1952, 1954 (Box 13:, Folder 506)
      - New Product Market Study Proposal, 1952 June (Box 13:, Folder 507)
      - Pattern Preferences Survey (no tabulations), 1952 (Box 13:, Folder 508)
      - Pattern Preferences Study, 1954 March (Box 13:, Folder 509)
      - Floor Coverings Design Preferences Survey (no tabulations), 1955 June (Box 13:, Folder 510)
      - Correspondence Re: Unidentified Dealer Study, 1957 February (Box 13:, Folder 511)
    - Continental Can Co., Inc.--Public Opinion and Marketing Study Proposal and Pilot Survey Tablualtions, 1945 April (Box 13:, Folder 512)
    - Crossley Inc.--Continuous Consumer Index (CCI)
      - Background, undated (Box 13:, Folder 513)
      - Canned Soup--Vol. I, No. 12, undated (Box 13:, Folder 514)
      - Laxatives and Cathartics, undated (Box 13:, Folder 515)
      - Canned Soup--Vol. I, No. 1, 1934 August (Box 13:, Folder 516)
      - Cereals--Vol. I, No. 1, 1934 August (Box 13:, Folder 517)
      - Coffee and Food Beverages--Vol. I, No. 1, 1934 August (Box 13:, Folder 518)
      - Dentifrices--Vol. I, No. 1, 1934 August (Box 13:, Folder 519)
      - Face Powders and Creams--Vol. I, No. 1, 1934 August (Box 13:, Folder 520)
      - Flour--Vol. I, No. 1, 1934 August (Box 13:, Folder 521)
      - Laxatives and Cathartics--Vol. I, No. 1, 1934 August (Box 13:, Folder 522)
      - Liniments and Cold Remedies--Vol. I, No. 1, 1934 August (Box 13:, Folder 523)
      - Soaps and Cleansers--Vol. I, No. 1, 1934 August (Box 13:, Folder 524)
      - Toilet Soaps--Vol. I, No. 1, 1934 August (Box 13:, Folder 525)
      - Cereals--Vol. I, No. 3, 1934 August - October (Box 13:, Folder 526)
      - Coffee and Food Beverages--Vol. I, No. 3, 1934 August - October (Box 13:, Folder 527)
      - Dentifrices--Vol. I, No. 3, 1934 August - October (Box 13:, Folder 528)
      - Face Powders and Creams--Vol. I, No. 3, 1934 August - October (Box 13:, Folder 529)
      - Flour--Vol. I, No. 3, 1934 August - October (Box 13:, Folder 530)
      - Laxatives and Cathartics--Vol. I, No. 3, 1934 August - October (Box 13:, Folder 531)
      - Liniments and Cold Remedies--Vol. I, No. 3, 1934 August - October (Box 13:, Folder 532)
      - Soaps and Cleansers--Vol. I, No. 3, 1934 August - October (Box 13:, Folder 533)
      - Toilet Soaps--Vol. I, No. 3, 1934 August - October (Box 13:, Folder 534)
      - Canned Soup--Vol. I, No. 6, 1934 August - 1935 January (Box 13:, Folder 535)
      - Cereals--Vol. I, No. 6, 1934 August - 1935 January (Box 13:, Folder 536)
      - Coffee and Food Beverages--Vol. I, No. 6, 1934 August - 1935 January (Box 13:, Folder 537)
      - Dentifrices--Vol. 1, No. 6, 1934 August - 1935 January (Box 13:, Folder 538)
      - Face Powders and Creams--Vol. I, No. 6, 1934 August - 1935 January (Box 13:, Folder 539)
      - Flour--Vol. I, No. 6, 1934 August - 1935 July (Box 13:, Folder 540)
      - Laxatives and Cathartics--Vol. I, No. 6, 1934 August - 1935 January (Box 13:, Folder 541)
      - Liniments and Cold Remedies--Vol. I, No. 6, 1934 August - 1935 January (Box 13:, Folder 542)
      - Soaps and Cleansers--Vol. I, No. 6, 1934 August - 1935 January (Box 13:, Folder 543)
      - Toilet Soaps--Vol. I, No. 6, 1934 August - 1935 January (Box 13:, Folder 544)
      - Canned Soup--Vol. I, No. 9, 1934 August - 1935 April (Box 13:, Folder 545)
      - Cereals--Vol. I, No. 9, 1934 August - 1935 April (Box 13:, Folder 546)
      - Coffee and Food Beverages--Vol. I, No. 9, 1934 August - 1935 April (Box 13:, Folder 547)
      - Dentifrices--Vol. I, No. 9, 1934 August - 1935 April (Box 13:, Folder 548)
      - Face Powders and Creams--Vol. I, No. 9, 1934 August - 1935 April (Box 13:, Folder 549)
      - Flour--Vol. I, No. 9, 1934 August - 1935 April (Box 13:, Folder 550)
      - Laxatives and Cathartics--Vol. I, No. 9, 1934 August - 1935 April (Box 13:, Folder 551)
      - Liniments and Cold Remedies--Vol. I, No. 9, 1934 August - 1935 April (Box 13:, Folder 552)
      - Soaps and Cleansers--Vol. I, No. 9, 1934 August - 1935 April (Box 13:, Folder 553)
      - Toilet Soaps--Vol. I, No. 9, 1934 August - 1935 April (Box 13:, Folder 554)
      - Cereals--Vol. I, No. 12, 1934 August - 1935 July (Box 13:, Folder 555)
      - Coffee and Food Beverages--Vol. I, No. 12, 1934 August - 1935 July (Box 13:, Folder 556)
      - Dentifrices--Vol. I, No. 12, 1934 August - 1935 July (Box 13:, Folder 557)
      - Face Powders and Creams--Vol. I, No. 12, 1934 August - 1935 July (Box 13:, Folder 558)
      - Flour--Vol. I, No. 12, 1934 August - 1935 July (Box 13:, Folder 559)
      - Laxatives and Cathartics--Vol. I, No. 12, 1934 August - 1935 July (Box 13:, Folder 560)
      - Liniments and Cold Remedies--Vol. I, No. 12, 1934 August - 1935 July (Box 13:, Folder 561)
      - Soaps and Cleansers--Vol. I, No. 12, 1934 August - 1935 July (Box 13:, Folder 562)
      - Toilet Soaps--Vol. I, No. 12, 1934 August - 1935 July (Box 13:, Folder 563)
      - Beers and Whiskies--Vol. I, No. 2, 1934 September (Box 13:, Folder 564)
      - Canned Soup--Vol. I, No. 2, 1934 September (Box 13:, Folder 565)
      - Cereals--Vol. I, No. 2, 1934 September (Box 13:, Folder 566)
      - Coffee and Food Beverages--Vol. I, No. 2, 1934 September (Box 13:, Folder 567)
      - Dentifrices--Vol. I, No. 2, 1934 September (Box 13:, Folder 568)
      - Face Powders and Creams--Vol. I, No. 2, 1934 September (Box 13:, Folder 569)
      - Flour--Vol. I, No. 2, 1934 September (Box 13:, Folder 570)
      - Laxatives and Cathartics--Vol. I, No. 2, 1934 September (Box 13:, Folder 571)
      - Liniments and Cold Remedies--Vol. I, No. 2, 1934 September (Box 13:, Folder 572)
      - Soaps and Cleansers--Vol. I, No. 2, 1934 September (Box 13:, Folder 573)
      - Toilet Soaps--Vol. I, No. 2, 1934 September (Box 13:, Folder 574)
      - Canned Soup--Vol. I, No. 3, 1934 October (Box 13:, Folder 575)
      - Cereals--Vol. I, No. 4, 1934 November (Box 13:, Folder 576)
      - Coffee and Food Beverages--Vol. I, No. 4, 1934 November (Box 13:, Folder 577)
      - Dentifrices--Vol. I, No. 4, 1934 November (Box 13:, Folder 578)
      - Face Powders and Creams--Vol. I, No. 4, 1934 November (Box 13:, Folder 579)
      - Flour--Vol. I, No. 4, 1934 November (Box 13:, Folder 580)
      - Laxatives and Cathartics--Vol. I, No. 4, 1934 November (Box 13:, Folder 581)
      - Liniments and Cold Remedies--Vol. I, No. 4, 1934 November (Box 13:, Folder 582)
      - Soaps and Cleansers--Vol. I, No. 4, 1934 November (Box 13:, Folder 583)
      - Toilet Soaps--Vol. I, No. 4, 1934 November (Box 13:, Folder 584)
      - Cereals--Vol. I, No. 5, 1934 December (Box 13:, Folder 585)
      - Coffee and Food Beverages--Vol. I, No. 5, 1934 December (Box 13:, Folder 586)
      - Dentifrices--Vol. I, No. 5, 1934 December (Box 13:, Folder 587)
      - Face Powders and Creams--Vol. I, No. 5, 1934 December (Box 13:, Folder 588)
      - Flour--Vol. I, No. 5, 1934 December (Box 13:, Folder 589)
      - Laxatives and Cathartics--Vol. I, No. 5, 1934 December (Box 13:, Folder 590)
      - Liniments and Cold Remedies--Vol. I, No. 5, 1934 December (Box 13:, Folder 591)
      - Soaps and Cleansers--Vol. I, No. 5, 1934 December (Box 13:, Folder 592)
      - Toilet Soaps--Vol. I, No. 5, 1934 December (Box 13:, Folder 593)
      - Canned Soup--Vol. I, No. 7, 1935 February (Box 13:, Folder 594)
      - Cereals--Vol. I, No. 7, 1935 February (Box 13:, Folder 595)
      - Coffee and Food Beverages--Vol. I, No. 7, 1935 February (Box 13:, Folder 596)
      - Dentifrices--Vol. I, No. 7, 1935 February (Box 13:, Folder 597)
      - Face Powders and Creams--Vol. I, No. 5, 1935 February (Box 13:, Folder 598)
      - Flour--Vol. I, No. 7, 1935 February (Box 13:, Folder 599)
      - Laxatives and Cathartics--Vol. I, No. 7, 1935 February (Box 13:, Folder 600)
      - Liniments and Cold Remedies--Vol. I, No. 7, 1935 February (Box 13:, Folder 601)
      - Soaps and Cleansers--Vol. I, No. 7, 1935 February (Box 13:, Folder 602)
      - Toilet Soaps--Vol. I, No. 7, 1935 February (Box 13:, Folder 603)
      - Canned Soup--Vol. I, No. 8, 1935 March (Box 14:, Folder 604)
      - Cereals--Vol. I, No. 8, 1935 March (Box 14:, Folder 605)
      - Coffee and Food Beverages--Vol. I, No. 8, 1935 March (Box 14:, Folder 606)
      - Dentifrices--Vol. I, No. 8, 1935 March (Box 14:, Folder 607)
      - Face Powders and Creams--Vol. I, No. 8, 1935 March (Box 14:, Folder 608)
      - Flour--Vol. I, No. 8, 1935 March (Box 14:, Folder 609)
      - Laxatives and Cathartics--Vol. I, No. 8, 1935 March (Box 14:, Folder 610)
      - Liniments and Cold Remedies--Vol. I, No. 8, 1935 March (Box 14:, Folder 611)
      - Soaps and Cleansers--Vol. I, No. 8, 1935 March (Box 14:, Folder 612)
      - Toilet Soaps--Vol. I, No. 8, 1935 March (Box 14:, Folder 613)
      - Canned Soup--Vol. I, No. 10, 1935 May (Box 14:, Folder 614)
      - Cereals--Vol. I, No. 10, 1935 May (Box 14:, Folder 615)
      - Coffee and Food Beverages--Vol. I, No. 10, 1935 May (Box 14:, Folder 616)
      - Dentifrices--Vol. I, No. 10, 1935 May (Box 14:, Folder 617)
      - Face Powders and Creams--Vol. I, No. 10, 1935 May (Box 14:, Folder 618)
      - Flour--Vol. I, No. 10, 1935 May (Box 14:, Folder 619)
      - Laxatives and Cathartics--Vol. I, No. 10, 1935 May (Box 14:, Folder 620)
      - Liniments and Cold Remedies--Vol. I, No. 10, 1935 May (Box 14:, Folder 621)
      - Soaps and Cleansers--Vol. I, No. 10, 1935 May (Box 14:, Folder 622)
      - Toilet Soaps--Vol. I, No. 10, 1935 May (Box 14:, Folder 623)
      - Canned Soup--Vol. I, No. 11, 1935 June (Box 14:, Folder 624)
      - Cereals--Vol. I, No. 11, 1935 June (Box 14:, Folder 625)
      - Coffee and Food Beverages--Vol. I, No. 11, 1935 June (Box 14:, Folder 626)
      - Dentifrices--Vol. I, No. 11, 1935 June (Box 14:, Folder 627)
      - Face Powders and Creams--Vol. I, No. 11, 1935 June (Box 14:, Folder 628)
      - Flour--Vol. I, No. 11, 1935 June (Box 14:, Folder 629)
      - Laxatives and Cathartics--Vol. I, No. 11, 1935 June (Box 14:, Folder 630)
      - Liniments and Cold Remedies--Vol. I, No. 11, 1935 June (Box 14:, Folder 631)
      - Soaps and Cleansers--Vol. I, No. 11, 1935 June (Box 14:, Folder 632)
      - Toilet Soaps--Vol. I, No. 11, 1935 June (Box 14:, Folder 633)
      - Canned Soup--Vol. I, No. 12, 1935 July (Box 14:, Folder 634)
      - Cereals--Vol. I, No. 12, 1935 July (Box 14:, Folder 635)
      - Coffee and Food Beverages--Vol. I, No. 11, 1935 July (Box 14:, Folder 636)
      - Dentifrices--Vol. I, No. 11, 1935 July (Box 14:, Folder 637)
      - Face Powders and Creams--Vol. I, No. 12, 1935 July (Box 14:, Folder 638)
      - Flour--Vol. I, No. 12, 1935 July (Box 14:, Folder 639)
      - Laxatives and Cathartics--Vol. I, No. 12, 1935 July (Box 14:, Folder 640)
      - Liniments and Cold Remedies--Vol. I, No. 12, 1935 July (Box 14:, Folder 641)
      - Soaps and Cleansers--Vol. I, No. 12, 1935 July (Box 14:, Folder 642)
      - Toilet Soaps--Vol. I, No. 12, 1935 July (Box 14:, Folder 643)
      - Canned Soup--Vol. II, No. 1, 1935 August (Box 14:, Folder 644)
      - Cereals--Vol. II, No. 1, 1935 August (Box 14:, Folder 645)
      - Coffee and Food Beverages--Vol. II, No. 1, 1935 August (Box 14:, Folder 646)
      - Crackers and Cookies--Vol. II, No. 1, 1935 August (Box 14:, Folder 647)
      - Dentifrices--Vol. II, No. 1, 1935 August (Box 14:, Folder 648)
      - Face Powders and Creams--Vol. II, No. 1, 1935 August (Box 14:, Folder 649)
      - Flour--Vol. II, No. 1, 1935 August (Box 14:, Folder 650)
      - Laxatives and Cathartics--Vol. II, No. 1, 1935 August (Box 14:, Folder 651)
      - Soaps and Cleansers--Vol. II, No. 1, 1935 August (Box 14:, Folder 652)
      - Canned Fruits and Vegetables--Vol. II, No. 2, 1935 September (Box 14:, Folder 653)
      - Canned Soup--Vol. II, No. 2, 1935 September (Box 14:, Folder 654)
      - Canned Tomato and Fruit Juices--Vol. II, No. 2, 1935 September (Box 14:, Folder 655)
      - Cereals--Vol. II, No. 2, 1935 September (Box 14:, Folder 656)
      - Coffee and Food Beverages--Vol. II, No. 2, 1935 September (Box 14:, Folder 657)
      - Dentifrices--Vol. II, No. 2, 1935 September (Box 14:, Folder 658)
      - Face Powders and Creams--Vol. II, No. 2, 1935 September (Box 14:, Folder 659)
      - Flour--Vol. II, No. 2, 1935 September (Box 14:, Folder 660)
      - Laxatives and Cathartics--Vol. II, No. 2, 1935 September (Box 14:, Folder 661)
      - Soaps and Cleansers--Vol. II, No. 2, 1935 September (Box 14:, Folder 662)
      - Canned Fruits and Vegetables--Vol. II, No. 3, 1935 October (Box 14:, Folder 663)
      - Canned Soup--Vol. II, No. 3, 1935 October (Box 14:, Folder 664)
      - Canned Tomato and Fruit Juices--Vol. II, No. 3, 1935 October (Box 14:, Folder 665)
      - Cereals--Vol. II, No. 3, 1935 October (Box 14:, Folder 666)
      - Coffee and Food Beverages--Vol. II, No. 3, 1935 October (Box 14:, Folder 667)
      - Dentifrices--Vol. II, No. 3, 1935 October (Box 14:, Folder 668)
      - Face Powders and Creams--Vol. II, No. 3, 1935 October (Box 14:, Folder 669)
      - Flour--Vol. II, No. 3, 1935 October (Box 14:, Folder 670)
      - Laxatives and Cathartics--Vol. II, No. 3, 1935 October (Box 14:, Folder 671)
      - Soaps and Cleansers--Vol. II, No. 3, 1935 October (Box 14:, Folder 672)
      - Canned Fruits and Vegetables--Vol. II, No. 4, 1935 November (Box 14:, Folder 673)
      - Canned Soup--Vol. II, No. 4, 1935 November (Box 14:, Folder 674)
      - Canned Tomato and Fruit Juices--Vol. II, No. 4, 1935 November (Box 14:, Folder 675)
      - Cereals--Vol. II, No. 4, 1935 November (Box 14:, Folder 676)
      - Coffee and Food Beverages--Vol. II, No. 4, 1935 November (Box 14:, Folder 677)
      - Dentifrices--Vol. II, No. 4, 1935 November (Box 14:, Folder 678)
      - Face Powders and Creams--Vol. II, No. 4, 1935 November (Box 14:, Folder 679)
      - Flour--Vol. II, No. 4, 1935 November (Box 14:, Folder 680)
      - Gelatin--Vol. II, No. 4, 1935 November (Box 14:, Folder 681)
      - Laxatives and Cathartics--Vol. II, No. 4, 1935 November (Box 14:, Folder 682)
      - Canned Fruits and Vegetables--Vol. II, No. 5, 1935 December (Box 14:, Folder 683)
      - Canned Tomato and Fruit Juices--Vol. II, No. 5, 1935 December (Box 14:, Folder 684)
      - Cereals--Vol. II, No. 5, 1935 December (Box 14:, Folder 685)
      - Coffee and Food Beverages--Vol. II, No. 5, 1935 December (Box 14:, Folder 686)
      - Dentifrices--Vol. II, No. 5, 1935 December (Box 14:, Folder 687)
      - Face Powders and Creams--Vol. II, No. 5, 1935 December (Box 14:, Folder 688)
      - Flour--Vol. II, No. 5, 1935 December (Box 14:, Folder 689)
      - Gelatin--Vol. II, No. 5, 1935 December (Box 14:, Folder 690)
      - Laxatives and Cathartics--Vol. II, No. 5, 1935 December (Box 14:, Folder 691)
      - Soaps and Cleansers--Vol. II, No. 5, 1935 December (Box 14:, Folder 692)
      - Canned Fruits and Vegetables--Vol. II, No. 6, 1936 January (Box 14:, Folder 693)
      - Canned Soup--Vol. II, No. 6, 1936 January (Box 14:, Folder 694)
      - Canned Tomato and Fruit Juices--Vol. II, No. 6, 1936 January (Box 14:, Folder 695)
      - Cereals--Vol. II, No. 6, 1936 January (Box 14:, Folder 696)
      - Coffee and Food Beverages--Vol. II, No. 5, 1936 January (Box 14:, Folder 697)
      - Dentifrices--Vol. II, No. 6, 1936 January (Box 14:, Folder 698)
      - Face Powders and Creams--Vol. II, No. 6, 1936 January (Box 14:, Folder 699)
      - Flour--Vol. II, No. 6, 1936 January (Box 14:, Folder 700)
      - Gelatin--Vol. II, No. 6, 1936 January (Box 14:, Folder 701)
      - Laxatives and Cathartics--Vol. II, No. 6, 1936 January (Box 14:, Folder 702)
      - Soaps and Cleansers--Vol. II, No. 6, 1936 January (Box 14:, Folder 703)
      - Canned Fruits and Vegetables--Vol. II, No. 7, 1936 February (Box 14:, Folder 704)
      - Canned Soup--Vol. II, No. 7, 1936 February (Box 14:, Folder 705)
      - Canned Tomato and Fruit Juices--Vol. II, No. 7, 1936 February (Box 14:, Folder 706)
      - Cereals--Vol. II, No. 7, 1936 February (Box 14:, Folder 707)
      - Coffee and Food Beverages--Vol. II, No. 7, 1936 February (Box 14:, Folder 708)
      - Dentifrices--Vol. II, No. 7, 1936 February (Box 14:, Folder 709)
      - Face Powders and Creams--Vol. II, No. 7, 1936 February (Box 14:, Folder 710)
      - Flour--Vol. II, No. 7, 1936 February (Box 14:, Folder 711)
      - Hand Lotions and Creams--Vol. II, No. 7, 1936 February (Box 14:, Folder 712)
      - Laxatives and Cathartics--Vol. II, No. 7, 1936 February (Box 14:, Folder 713)
      - Soaps and Cleansers--Vol. II, No. 7, 1936 February (Box 14:, Folder 714)
      - Canned Fruits and Vegetables--Vol. II, No. 8, 1936 March (Box 14:, Folder 715)
      - Canned Soup--Vol. II, No. 8, 1936 March (Box 14:, Folder 716)
      - Canned Tomato and Fruit Juices--Vol. II, No. 8, 1936 March (Box 14:, Folder 717)
      - Cereals--Vol. II, No. 8, 1936 March (Box 14:, Folder 718)
      - Coffee and Food Beverages--Vol. II, No. 8, 1936 March (Box 14:, Folder 719)
      - Dentifrices--Vol. II, No. 8, 1936 March (Box 14:, Folder 720)
      - Face Powders and Creams--Vol. II, No. 8, 1936 March (Box 14:, Folder 721)
      - Flour--Vol. II, No. 8, 1936 March (Box 14:, Folder 722)
      - Gelatin--Vol. II, No. 8, 1936 March (Box 14:, Folder 723)
      - Soaps and Cleansers--Vol. II, No. 8, 1936 March (Box 14:, Folder 724)
      - Canned Fruits and Vegetables--Vol. II, No. 9, 1936 April (Box 14:, Folder 725)
      - Canned Soup--Vol. II, No. 9, 1936 April (Box 14:, Folder 726)
      - Canned Tomato and Fruit Juices--Vol. II, No. 9, 1936 April (Box 14:, Folder 727)
      - Cereals--Vol. II, No. 9, 1936 April (Box 14:, Folder 728)
      - Coffee and Food Beverages--Vol. II, No. 9, 1936 April (Box 14:, Folder 729)
      - Dentifrices--Vol. II, No. 9, 1936 April (Box 14:, Folder 730)
      - Face Powders and Creams--Vol. II, No. 9, 1936 April (Box 14:, Folder 731)
      - Flour--Vol. II, No. 9, 1936 April (Box 14:, Folder 732)
      - Gelatin--Vol. II, No. 9, 1936 April (Box 14:, Folder 733)
      - Laxatives and Cathartics--Vol. II, No. 9, 1936 April (Box 14:, Folder 734)
      - Soaps and Cleansers--Vol. II, No. 9, 1936 April (Box 14:, Folder 735)